[Plot Love II]
[مؤامرة الحب الثاني]
[Episode 18]
[الحلقة 18]
Sister,
أخت،
you'd better not go in yet.
من الأفضل ألا تدخل بعد.
Grandma can't get stimulated any more.
لا يمكن للجدة أن تتحفز بعد الآن.
Come to see grandma
تعال لرؤية الجدة
when she gets better.
عندما تتحسن.
All right.
حسنا.
Okay.
تمام.
Is grandma okay?
هل الجدة بخير؟
She hasn't woken up yet.
لم تستيقظ بعد.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Go back to rest.
ارجع للراحة.
When grandma wakes up, I will take her back.
عندما تستيقظ جدتي ، سأعيدها.
Okay.
تمام.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
Grandma.
الجدة.
Grandma, you are awake.
جدتي ، أنتِ مستيقظة.
Slow down.
ابطئ.
Take care.
يعتني.
Grandma.
الجدة.
Are you
أنت
feeling comfortable now?
تشعر بالراحة الآن؟
You must be hungry.
لابد أنكم جوعى.
I am going to...
انا ذاهب الى...
Go find Su Bei.
اذهب وابحث عن Su Bei.
Grandma.
الجدة.
No more angry words.
لا مزيد من الكلمات الغاضبة.
They are not angry words.
إنها ليست كلمات غاضبة.
You don't care about me
أنت لا تهتم بي
anyway.
على أي حال.
Grandma, calm down.
جدتي ، اهدئي.
Take some water.
خذ بعض الماء.
Grandma.
الجدة.
My brother has always been filial.
كان أخي دائمًا ابنًا.
When you asked him to marry the daughter of the Su family,
عندما طلبت منه الزواج من ابنة عائلة سو ،
he agreed directly.
وافق مباشرة.
Grandma, forgive him this time.
جدتي اغفر له هذه المرة.
He will definitely listen to you in the future.
سوف يستمع إليك بالتأكيد في المستقبل.
If so,
لو ذلك،
I'll arrange blind dates for you.
سأرتب لك مواعيد عمياء.
Grandma.
الجدة.
Brother.
أخ.
Stop pissing off grandma.
توقف عن تبول الجدة.
♪Another♪
♪ آخر ♪
Just for Su Bei?
فقط من أجل Su Bei؟
You...
أنت...
Aren't you going to recognize me as grandma?
ألن تتعرف علي كجدة؟
What if
ماذا إذا
I insist that the two of you break up?
أصر على أن ينفصل كلاكما؟
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
أحدق في حافة النافذة
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪ تلك الزهرة الساقطة لم تعد تتفتح
Lu Nan.
لو نان.
♪You always say♪
♪ أنت دائما تقول ♪
I know that
وأنا أعلم ذلك
you signed an agreement with me
لقد وقعت اتفاقية معي
and was together with me
وكان معي
in order to
بغرض
satisfy your grandma's wish.
إرضاء رغبة جدتك.
But I can feel
لكن يمكنني أن أشعر
how well you treated me during this time.
كيف تعاملت معي بشكل جيد خلال هذا الوقت.
Thank you
شكرًا لك
for making me feel like I'm not alone anymore.
لجعلني أشعر أنني لست وحدي بعد الآن.
It's a pity that
إنه لأمر مؤسف أن
I can't give your grandma
لا أستطيع أن أعطي جدتك
what she wants.
ماذا تريد.
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪ ما مدى سعادتك بالضحك
I don't want you to be caught in a dilemma
لا أريدك أن تقع في مأزق
between me and my grandma.
بيني وبين جدتي.
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪ أنت تخططين لمستقبلك معها
Grandma treats you well.
الجدة تعاملك معاملة حسنة.
This kind of kinship
هذا النوع من القرابة
is beyond my reach.
بعيد المنال.
You have to cherish it.
عليك أن تعتز به.
Don't let down your grandma's love for you.
لا تخذل حب جدتك لك.
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
As for us...
بالنسبة لنا...
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪
Let's give each other some more time,
دعونا نعطي بعضنا البعض المزيد من الوقت ،
shall we?
هلا فعلنا؟
Hello, the number you dialed is power off.
مرحبًا ، الرقم الذي طلبته مغلق.
♪Still listening♪
♪ ما زلت تستمع ♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪
An Ning.
نينغ.
I am here to see you again.
أنا هنا لأراك مرة أخرى.
Every year at this time
كل عام في هذا الوقت
I want to see you.
أريد أن أراك.
I wonder if you are living a good life in heaven.
أتساءل عما إذا كنت تعيش حياة طيبة في الجنة.
[Tomb of Beloved Wife An Ning]
[قبر الزوجة الحبيبة أن نينغ]
I don't know if there are irises there.
لا أعرف ما إذا كانت هناك قزحية.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
the irises we raised at home?
القزحية التي أثيرناها في المنزل؟
I remember at that time,
أتذكر في ذلك الوقت ،
you always complained
كنت دائما تشتكي
about my
عني
poor watering control.
ضعف التحكم في الري.
At that time, I thought it was so troublesome to grow flowers,
في ذلك الوقت ، اعتقدت أنه من الصعب جدًا زراعة الأزهار ،
why bother?
لماذا تهتم؟
But I'm pretty proficient now.
لكنني ماهر جدًا الآن.
I thought that
وأعتقد أن
meeting Lu Nan
لقاء لو نان
was my greatest luck.
كان حظي الأكبر.
We've been through so much together,
لقد مررنا بالكثير معًا ،
and it's hard to get to where we are now.
ومن الصعب الوصول إلى ما نحن عليه الآن.
I didn't believe in feelings before.
لم أكن أؤمن بالمشاعر من قبل.
But now I finally
لكني الآن أخيرًا
have expectations for relationships.
لديها توقعات للعلاقات.
I really like him.
أنا أحبه حقًا.
But I don't know
لكني لا أعرف
why everything
لماذا كل شيء
turned out this way.
تحولت بهذه الطريقة.
Mom.
أم.
What should I do?
ماذا علي أن أفعل؟
Before,
قبل،
as long as I had time,
طالما كان لدي وقت ،
I would cook for you at home.
أود أن أطبخ لك في المنزل.
But you always wanted to learn to cook by yourself.
لكنك أردت دائمًا أن تتعلم الطبخ بنفسك.
Do you remember
هل تذكر
one time you blew up the kitchen?
ذات مرة فجرت المطبخ؟
I've never let you
أنا لم أدعك أبدا
touch the cooktop since then.
المس الموقد منذ ذلك الحين.
You are such a fool.
يا لك من أحمق.
How can you take care of yourself?
كيف يمكنك الاعتناء بنفسك؟
As long as I can be with you all the time,
طالما يمكنني أن أكون معك طوال الوقت ،
I am willing
انا أرغب
to cook every day.
لطهي الطعام كل يوم.
What to do?
ماذا أفعل؟
After all these years,
بعد كل هذه السنوات،
I still can't forget you.
ما زلت لا أستطيع أن أنساك.
An Ning.
نينغ.
I miss you so much.
أفتقدك كثيرًا.
Mom.
أم.
I really miss you.
أنا حقاً أفتقدك.
I thought
اعتقدت
my dad was my only relative
كان والدي هو قريبي الوحيد
in this world.
في هذا العالم.
But he didn't take my feelings into consideration at all.
لكنه لم يأخذ مشاعري بعين الاعتبار على الإطلاق.
For the sake of the company
من أجل الشركة
and Su Manni,
وسو ماني ،
he doesn't care
لا يهتم
who I marry at all.
الذين أتزوجهم على الإطلاق.
He doesn't care whether I like him or not,
لا يهمني ما إذا كنت أحبه أم لا ،
and whether I am happy or not.
وهل أنا سعيد أم لا.
If you were there,
إذا كنت هناك ،
you wouldn't agree with him.
لن تتفق معه.
Are you
أنت
Mr. Ye Haochen?
السيد يي Haochen؟
Yes, it's me.
نعم هذا انا.
You know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
I am also a designer.
انا ايضا مصمم
I have seen your work.
لقد رأيت عملك.
Thanks.
شكرًا.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
My name is Su Bei.
اسمي Su Bei.
Su Bei?
مع باي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Aren't you Su Bei
ألست Su Bei
who represented Huanzhen in the Angel's Covenant Contest?
من الذي مثل Huanzhen في مسابقة عهد الملائكة؟
You know me?
أنت تعرفني؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
You are the champion of the preliminary round.
أنت بطل الدور التمهيدي.
I was very impressed
لقد تأثرت كثيرا
by your work Moonlight in Starry Sky.
من خلال عملك ضوء القمر في السماء المرصعة بالنجوم.
The work itself is lively,
العمل نفسه مفعم بالحيوية ،
and the creativity can strike a chord.
ويمكن للإبداع أن يضرب على وتر حساس.
Thank you, Mr. Ye.
شكرا لك يا سيد.
Mr. Ye, thank you for taking me back.
السيد يي ، شكرا لك على إعادتي.
You are welcome.
مرحباً بك.
It's too remote to take a taxi.
إنه بعيد جدًا عن ركوب سيارة أجرة.
And it's on my way home.
وهو في طريقي إلى المنزل.
Mr. Ye, is this your design work?
السيد يي ، هل هذا عمل التصميم الخاص بك؟
Yes, an unfinished design.
نعم ، تصميم غير مكتمل.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
It doesn't matter. You can directly tell me
لا يهم.  يمكنك إخباري مباشرة
about your idea.
حول فكرتك.
I feel like something is missing here.
أشعر أن شيئًا ما مفقود هنا.
So what do you think is missing here?
إذن ما الذي تعتقد أنه مفقود هنا؟
If it were me,
لو كنت أنا،
I would add some Sichuan embroidery elements.
أود أن أضيف بعض عناصر التطريز في سيتشوان.
Sichuan embroidery elements?
عناصر التطريز سيتشوان؟
Yes.
نعم.
Sorry.
آسف.
Did I say something wrong?
هل قلت شيئا خاطئا؟
I shouldn't have pointed fingers at your work.
لا ينبغي أن أشير بأصابع الاتهام إلى عملك.
Not at all.
لا على الاطلاق.
I think you are right.
أعتقد أنك على حق.
Actually, I thought
في الواقع ، اعتقدت
there was something missing here.
كان هناك شيء مفقود هنا.
But...
ولكن...
You are talented in costume design.
أنت موهوب في تصميم الأزياء.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Su Bei.
مع باي.
To tell you the truth,
لأقول لك الحقيقة،
I plan to start my own clothing brand.
أخطط لبدء ماركة الملابس الخاصة بي.
Are you interested in
هل انت مهتم في
being a designer for my new brand?
كوني مصمم لعلامتي التجارية الجديدة؟
Thank you for acknowledging me.
شكرا لك على الاعتراف بي.
But probably not this time.
لكن ربما ليس هذه المرة.
Because of Huanzhen?
بسبب Huanzhen؟
Yes.
نعم.
Never mind.
لا تهتم.
I can wait for you.
أستطيع إنتظارك.
Think about it again.
فكر في الأمر مرة أخرى.
You can reply to me
يمكنك الرد علي
after the contest is over.
بعد انتهاء المسابقة.
Mr. Ye,
السيد.  هو،
thank you for bringing me back today.
شكرا لك على إعادتي اليوم.
You are welcome.
مرحباً بك.
Why are you together?
لماذا انتم معا
♪Another♪
♪ آخر ♪
♪Long talk all night♪
♪ حديث طويل طوال الليل ♪
♪I haven't finished drinking the water on the table♪
لم أنتهي من شرب الماء على المائدة
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
أحدق في حافة النافذة
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪ تلك الزهرة الساقطة لم تعد تتفتح
♪You always say♪
♪ أنت دائما تقول ♪
♪Like and love♪
♪ اعجاب وحب ♪
♪Are similar but different♪
♪ متشابهة لكنها مختلفة ♪
♪Finally this time I'm being depended on too♪
♪ أخيرًا هذه المرة أنا أعتمد أيضًا
♪Listen and cover up, learn to sigh♪
♪ استمع وتستر وتعلم التنهد ♪
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪ ما مدى سعادتك بالضحك
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪ أنت تخططين لمستقبلك معها
♪I'm so numb, but I'm♪
♪ أنا مخدر جدًا ، لكنني ♪
♪Still listening♪
♪ ما زلت تستمع ♪
♪I don't have to guess your mind anymore♪
♪ ليس عليّ أن أخمن عقلك بعد الآن ♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪